Guide to the Donald Pippin Collection MUS.0003
Music Library
- Reviews, circa 1967-2011; 274 computer file(s) 274 TIF facsimiles
  - Don Pasquale - San Ramon Valley Times, 1995 March 10; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Seabury, Roberta; Donizetti, Gaetano
  - Don Pasquale - San Francisco Chronicle; Rita - Palo Alto Times; Teseo - Sacramento Bee; Pippin - San Francisco Chronicle; Julius Caesar - San Francisco Chronicle; Xerxes - San Francisco Chronicle; King for a day - Oakland Tribune; King for a day - San Francisco Chronicle; Tutor in a tangle - San Francisco Chronicle; Acis and Galatea - Oakland Tribune; Julius Caesar - Palo Alto Times, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    - Don Pasquale - San Francisco Chronicle, undated
    - Rita - Palo Alto Times, undated
    - Teseo - Sacramento Bee, undated
    - Pippin comment - San Francisco Chronicle, undated
    - Julius Caesar - San Francisco Chronicle, undated
    - Xerxes - San Francisco Chronicle, undated
    - King for a day - Oakland Tribune, undated
      Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901
    - Tutor in a tangle - San Francisco Chronicle, undated
    - Acis and Galatea - Oakland Tribune, undated
    - Julius Caesar - Palo Alto Times, undated
  - Don Pasquale, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Halsey, Jan; Donizetti, Gaetano
  - Don Pasquale - Oakland Tribune, 1976 August 12; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Hertelendy, Paul; Donizetti, Gaetano
  - Don Pasquale - San Francisco Chronicle, 1976 August 10; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Donizetti, Gaetano; Commanday, Robert
  - Don Procopio / Marriage by lantern - San Jose Mercury News, 1989 May 11; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Bizet, Georges; Offenbach, Jacques, 1819-1880; Hertelendy, Paul
  - Don Procopio / Marriage by lantern - San Francisco Chronicle, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Offenbach, Jacques, 1819-1880; Bizet, Georges; Tucker, Marilyn
  - Eugene Onegin, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Tchaikovsky, Peter Ilich; Hertelendy, Paul
  - Eugene Onegin - Peninsula Times-Tribune, 1983 March 21; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Smith, Karen; Tchaikovsky, Peter Ilich
  - Falstaff - San Francisco Classical Voice, 2001 June 17; 3 computer file(s) 3 TIF facsimiles
    Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901; Tircuit, Heuwell
  - Imeneo - Oakland Tribune, 1977 February 2; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759; Hertelendy, Paul
  - Imeneo - San Francisco Chronicle; Pippin 25th anniversary - San Francisco Chronicle, 1977 February 1; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    - Imeneo - San Francisco Chronicle, 1977 February 1
    - Pippin 25th anniversary - San Francisco Chronicle, 1977 February 1
      Caen, Herb
  - Italian girl in Algiers - San Francisco Chronicle, 1980 February 12; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Commanday, Robert; Rossini, Gioacchino
  - Italian girl in Algiers - Sacramento Union, 1980 February 14; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Rossini, Gioacchino; Simon, Richard
  - Italian girl in Algiers - San Jose Mercury, 1980 February 12; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Italian girl in Algiers - Times, 1980 February 20; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Bladen, Barbara; Rossini, Gioacchino
  - Italian girl in Algiers - San Francisco Sunday Examiner and Chronicle, 1980 February 17; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Walsh, Michael; Rossini, Gioacchino
  - Italian girl in Algiers - Sentinel, 1980 February 22; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Rossini, Gioacchino; Ballantyne, Donald
  - Italian girl in Algiers - Post, 1983 March 16; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Rossini, Gioacchino; Gereben, Janos
  - Italian girl in Algiers, 1983 March 20; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Rossini, Gioacchino; Livingstone, Janet
  - Italian girl in Algiers - Peninsula Times Tribune, 1980 February 25; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Rossini, Gioacchino; Ratliff, William
  - Italian girl in Algiers - Peninsula Times Tribune, 1983 March 15; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Smith, Karen; Rossini, Gioacchino
  - Italian girl in Algiers, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Italian girl in Algiers - Voice, 1987 February 11; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Julius Caesar, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Hertelendy, Paul; Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759
  - Julius Caesar - San Francisco Chronicle, 1977 March 8; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Julius Caesar - San Francisco Chronicle, 1979 July 24; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Julius Caesar; Rake's Progress, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759; Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971
  - Julius Caesar, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - King for a day, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901; Bloomfield, Arthur
  - King for a day - Oakland Tribune, 1975 August 5; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901; Hertelendy, Paul
  - King for a day - Union, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901; Myers, Robert N.
  - King for a day - San Francisco Chronicle, 1975 August 5; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Commanday, Robert; Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901
  - King for a day - San Francisco Chronicle, 1981 February 17; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901; Tucker, Marilyn
  - King for a day, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901; Livingstone, Janet
  - Lucia di Lammermoor - San Francisco Examiner, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Donizetti, Gaetano; Pontzious, Richard L.
  - Lucia di Lammermoor - Peninsula Times-Tribune, 1983 March 28; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Donizetti, Gaetano; Owen, Angela M.
  - Maria Padilla - San Jose Mercury News, 1983 April 16; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Maria Padilla - San Francisco Chronicle, 1984 January 19; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Donizetti, Gaetano; Tucker, Marilyn
  - Maria Padilla - San Francisco Examiner, 1984 January 18; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Beach, Scott; Donizetti, Gaetano
  - Maria Padilla - Peninsula Times-Tribune, 1983 April 18; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Maves, C. E. (Carl); Donizetti, Gaetano
  - Maria Padilla - Berkeley Gazette, 1983 April 22; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Donizetti, Gaetano; Livingstone, Janet
  - Maria Padilla - Sentinel, 1984 February 2; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Donizetti, Gaetano; Huck, Bill
  - Maria Padilla - Los Angeles Times, 1983 April 22; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Donizetti, Gaetano; Ulrich, Allan
  - Maria Padilla - KCSM Radio, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Maria Padilla - Sentinel, 1983 April 28; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Huck, Bill; Donizetti, Gaetano
  - Maria Padilla - San Francisco Chronicle, 1983 April 19; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Marriage of Figaro - Opera News, 1981 September 6; 2 computer file(s) 2 TIF facsimiles
  - Marriage of Figaro - San Jose Mercury News, 1981 April 8; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Marriage of Figaro - Opera News, 1981 September 6; 2 computer file(s) 2 TIF facsimiles
  - Marriage of Figaro, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Marriage of Figaro - San Francisco Chronicle, 1981 May 5; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Tucker, Marilyn; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791
  - Marriage of Figaro - Tribune, 1981 April 7; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Shere, Charles; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791
  - Marriage of Figaro - San Francisco Examiner, 1981 April 6; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791; Ulrich, Allan
  - Marriage of Figaro - Montclarion, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Livingstone, Janet; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791
  - Marriage of Figaro - San Francisco Chronicle, 1989 May 25; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791; Tucker, Marilyn
  - Marriage of Figaro - Sun-Reporter, 1995 February 23; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791; Ohman, Eleanor
  - Marriage of Figaro - San Diego Reader, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791; Saville, Jonathan
  - Martha - San Jose Mercury News, 1982 July 13; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Flotow, Friedrich von, 1812-1883; Hertelendy, Paul
  - Martha - San Francisco Examiner, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Flotow, Friedrich von, 1812-1883; Pontzious, Richard L.
  - Martha - Peninsula Times-Tribune, 1983 February 22; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Ratliff, William; Flotow, Friedrich von, 1812-1883
  - Martha, 1988 February 1; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Flotow, Friedrich von, 1812-1883; Wakeland, Jeanie R.
  - Martha, 1982 July 25; 3 computer file(s) 3 TIF facsimiles
    Flotow, Friedrich von, 1812-1883; Provoo, George
  - Martha / King for a day / Don Pasquale / Merry widow - Stockton Record, 1986 December 8; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Lehár, Franz; Flotow, Friedrich von, 1812-1883; Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901; Runion, Dianne; Donizetti, Gaetano
  - Mary Stuart, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Donizetti, Gaetano; Maves, C. E. (Carl)
  - Mary Stuart, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Merry widow - Bay Area Reporter, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Drewes, Stephen; Lehár, Franz
  - Merry widow - San Francisco Examiner, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Lehár, Franz; Hurwitt, Robert
  - Merry widow - Tribune, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Yim, Roger; Lehár, Franz
  - Merry widow - Peninsula Times-Tribune, 1986 September 24; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Lehár, Franz; Ratliff, William
  - Merry widow - San Jose Mercury News, 1986 September 22; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Lehár, Franz; Hertelendy, Paul
  - Merry wives of Windsor, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Pfaff, Tim; Nicolai, Otto
  - Merry wives of Windsor - Oakland Tribune, 1984 February 21; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Shere, Charles; Nicolai, Otto
  - Merry wives of Windsor - San Francisco Chronicle, 1983 July 12; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Commanday, Robert; Nicolai, Otto
  - Merry wives of Windsor - California Voice, 1984 February 23-29; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Nicolai, Otto; Leighton, Donald
  - Merry wives of Windsor / Italian girl in Algiers / Don Pasquale - Peninsula Times-Tribune, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Rossini, Gioacchino; Smith, Karen; Donizetti, Gaetano; Nicolai, Otto
  - Musical offering, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Fried, Alexander; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750
  - My fair Galatea / Education incomplete - San Francisco Chronicle, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Suppé, Franz von; Tucker, Marilyn; Chabrier, Emmanuel
  - My fair Galatea / Education incomplete - San Jose Mercury News, 1989 April 27; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Hertelendy, Paul; Chabrier, Emmanuel; Suppé, Franz von
  - My fair Galatea / Education incomplete - San Francisco Examiner, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Chabrier, Emmanuel; Ulrich, Allan; Suppé, Franz von
  - No love allowed - San Jose Mercury News, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883; Hertelendy, Paul
  - No love allowed, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883
  - No love allowed - Musical America, 1990 July; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883; Moor, Paul
  - No love allowed - San Francisco Chronicle, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883; Kosman, Joshua
  - Norma; Yanked from the harem; Abu Hassan; Belty, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791; Huck, Bill; Donizetti, Gaetano; Bellini, Vincenzo; Weber, Carl Maria von
  - Orpheus in the underworld / Vie Parisienne - Bay Guardian, 1985 August 21; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Orlando - San Francisco Chronicle, 1973 September 18; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Orlando - San Francisco Chronicle, 1974 August 13; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Orlando - Palo Alto Times, 1978 August 15; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759; Maves, C. E. (Carl)
  - Orlando - Peninsula Times-Tribune, 1983 March 1; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759; Crawford, Caroline (Caroline Cooley)
  - Orpheus in the underworld - Peninsula Times-Tribune, 1985 August 1; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Smith, Karen; Offenbach, Jacques, 1819-1880
  - Orpheus in the underworld - San Francisco Chronicle, 1985 August 2; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Périchole - San Francisco Chronicle, 1984 August 7; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Tircuit, Heuwell; Offenbach, Jacques, 1819-1880
  - Périchole - Davis Enterprise, 1984 July 12; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Offenbach, Jacques, 1819-1880; McColm, Del
  - Périchole - Woodland Democrat, 1984 July 12; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Offenbach, Jacques, 1819-1880; Bang, Derrick
  - Périchole - Sacramento Union, 1984 July 13; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Offenbach, Jacques, 1819-1880; Simon, Richard
  - Périchole - Post, 1984 August 1; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Gereben, Janos; Offenbach, Jacques, 1819-1880
  - Périchole - Peninsula Times-Tribune, 1984 February 13; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Offenbach, Jacques, 1819-1880; Smith, Karen
  - Piano recital, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Chopin, Frédéric; Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918; Scarlatti, Alessandro, 1660-1725; Pace, David
  - Pick of the Pockets - Caramel Pine Cone, 1995 September 28; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Plotkin, Nathalie
  - Pimpinone, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Telemann, Georg Philipp, 1681-1767
  - Pimpinone, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Telemann, Georg Philipp, 1681-1767; Hertelendy, Paul
  - Pippin article - Opera News, undated; 2 computer file(s) 2 TIF facsimiles
    Von Buchau, Stephanie
  - Pippin article (partial) - (Opera News), undated; 2 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Pippin on Handel operas, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Commanday, Robert
  - Pippin article - (Opera News), undated; 2 computer file(s) 2 TIF facsimiles
  - Pippin article - West Bay Today, 1976 October 10; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Marcoux, Janice
  - Pippin on Handel operas, 1977 March 6; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Pippin article - San Francisco Examiner, 1979 April 25; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Chapin, Dwight
  - Pippin article - San Francisco Examiner, 1982 March 11; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Pontzious, Richard L.
  - Pippin article - San Francisco Bay Guardian, 1986 August 6; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Livingstone, Janet
  - Pippin article - Berkeley Monthly, 1983 June; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Pippin article - Berkeley Gazette, 1983 June 10; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Pippin article - Hope, 1998 July; 3 computer file(s) 3 TIF facsimiles
    Roy, Karen
  - Pippin - San Francisco Examiner; Pippin - San Diego Reader; Pippin - Sacramento Bee; Pippin - San Francisco Sentinel; Pippin - Berkeley Voice; Cenerentola - San Francisco Chronicle; Italian girl in Algiers - Voice; Don Pasquale - San Francisco Chronicle; Marriage of Figaro - San Francisco Sentinel; Cosi fan tutte - Oakland Tribune; Cosi fan tutte - San Francisco Chronicle; Abduction from the seraglio - San Francisco Sentinel; Merry widow - Oakland Tribune; Merry widow - Bay Area Reporter; Lucia di Lammermoor - San Francisco Examiner; Belle Helene - San Francisco Chroncle; Orpheus in the underworld - Los Angeles Times; Orpheus in the underworld - San Francisco Commanday; Bridge of sighs - Berkeley Voice; Princess of Tebizonde - Stockton Record; Vie Parisienne - San Francisco Chronicle; Merry wives of Windsor - Daily Californian, undated; 2 computer file(s) 2 TIF facsimiles
    - Pippin comment - San Francisco Examiner, undated
    - Pippin comment - San Diego Reader, undated
      Saville, Jonathan
    - Pippin comment - Sacramento Bee, undated
      Masullo, Robert A.
    - Pippin comment - San Francisco Sentinel, undated
      Huck, Bill
    - Pippin comment - Berkeley Voice, undated
    - Cenerentola - San Francisco Chronicle, undated
    - Italian girl in Algiers - Voice, undated
    - Don Pasquale - San Francisco Chronicle, undated
    - Marriage of figaro - San Francisco Sentinel, undated
      Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791; Huck, Bill
    - Cosi fan tutte - Oakland Tribune, undated
    - Cosi fan tutte - San Francisco Chronicle, undated
    - Yanked from the harem - San Francisco Sentinel, undated
      Huck, Bill; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791
    - Merry widow - Oakland Tribune, undated
    - Merry widow - Bay Area Reporter, undated
    - Lucia di Lammermoor - San Francisco Examiner, undated
    - Belle Helene - San Francisco Chronicle, undated
    - Orpheus in the underworld - Los Angeles Times, undated
    - Orpheus in the underworld - San Francisco Chronicle, undated
      Commanday, Robert; Offenbach, Jacques, 1819-1880
    - Bridge of sighs - Berkeley Voice, undated
    - Princess of Trebizonde - Stockton Record, undated
      Offenbach, Jacques, 1819-1880; Runion, Dianne
    - Vie Parisienne - San Francisco Chronicle, undated
    - Merry wives of Windsor - Daily Californian, undated
  - Pippin birthday concert, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Pippin birthday / Opera introductions - San Francisco Classical Voice, 2011 December 13; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Pippin birthday concert - Sacramento Bee, 1984 December 11; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Pocket Opera article - Voice, 1980 March 21; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Ariel
  - Pocket Opera's season no. 35 - San Francisco Classical Voice, 2011 December 13; 2 computer file(s) 2 TIF facsimile
  - Pocket Opera Company - San Francisco Magazine, 2000 July; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Gioia, Dana
  - Pocket Opera article - Voice, 1980 March 21; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Princess of Trebizonde - Opera Guide, 1987 February 28; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Carr, R. T.; Offenbach, Jacques, 1819-1880
  - Princess of Trebizonde - San Francisco Chronicle, 1986 April 23; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Offenbach, Jacques, 1819-1880; Tircuit, Heuwell
  - Princess of Trebizonde - San Francisco Examiner, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Pontzious, Richard L.; Offenbach, Jacques, 1819-1880
  - Princess of Trebizonde - Montclarion, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Princess of Trebizonde - Sacramento Bee, 1987 April 6; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Princess of Trebizonde - Oakland Tribune, 1987 April 6; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Princess of Trebizonde - Stockton Record, 1986 June 16; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Princess of Trebizonde - San Francisco Chronicle, 1986 April 23; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Rake's progress - Peninsula Times-Tribune, 1979 August 31; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971; Ratliff, William
  - Rinaldo - San Francisco Chronicle, 1982 June 22; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Tircuit, Heuwell
  - Rinaldo, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759; Pontzious, Richard L.
  - Rita, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Donizetti, Gaetano; Earle, Anitra
  - Secret marriage - San Francisco Chronicle, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Cimarosa, Domenico; Kosman, Joshua
  - Semele - San Francisco Examiner, 1969 August 11; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759; Bloomfield, Arthur
  - Semele, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Serva padrona - Carmel Pine Cone, 1973 September; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Pergolesi, Giovanni Battista
  - Serva padrona - Monterey Peninsula Herald, 1973 September 3; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Seymour, Richard; Pergolesi, Giovanni Battista
  - Serva padrona - Sacramento Bee, 1973 April 30; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Pergolesi, Giovanni Battista; Fanning, Garth
  - Songstress - San Francisco Chronicle, 1973 January 30; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Tircuit, Heuwell; Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809
  - Stiffelio - San Francisco Chronicle, 1979 August 14; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Stiffelio - San Jose Mercury and News, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901; Pontzious, Richard L.
  - Stiffelio - Peninsula Times, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Maves, C. E. (Carl); Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901
  - Stiffelio / Anna Bolena - San Francisco Magazine, 1980 November; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901; Von Buchau, Stephanie; Donizetti, Gaetano
  - Stiffelio / King for a day / Tutor in a tangle / Cosi fan tutte, 1979 August; 5 computer file(s) 5 TIF facsimiles
    Sullivan, Gwyn; Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901; Donizetti, Gaetano; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791
  - Teseo - Oakland Tribune; Schubert piano recital - San Francisco Chronicle, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    - Teseo - Oakland Tribune, undated
    - Schubert piano recital - San Francisco Chronicle, undated
  - Teseo - Voice, 1983 February 25; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Ariel; Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759
  - Teseo - Peninsula Times-Tribune, 1983 February 16; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759; Smith, Karen
  - Tutor in a tangle, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Donizetti, Gaetano; Tircuit, Heuwell
  - Tutor in a tangle - San Francisco Examiner, 1977 August 8; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Donizetti, Gaetano; Bloomfield, Arthur
  - Tutor in a tangle - Palo Alto Times, 1978 May 22; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Nichols, Dorothy; Donizetti, Gaetano
  - Tutor in a tangle - Oakland Tribune, 1982 March 29; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Donizetti, Gaetano; Shere, Charles
  - Two widows, 1984 February 11; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Smetana, Bedřich; Livingstone, Janet
  - Two widows - Peninsula Times-Tribune, 1984 February 7; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Smith, Karen; Smetana, Bedřich
  - Two widows, 1981 August 30; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Smetana, Bedřich
  - Two widows, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Smetana, Bedřich; Leighton, Donald
  - Vie Parisienne - Peninsula Times Tribune, 1984 August 3; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Ratliff, William; Offenbach, Jacques, 1819-1880
  - Vie Parisienne - Ann Arbor News, 1985 July 15; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Offenbach, Jacques, 1819-1880; Leonard, Jim
  - Vie Parisienne - San Francisco Examiner, 1981 July 20; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Vie Parisienne - San Francisco Chronicle, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Vie Parisienne - San Francisco Chronicle, 1981 July 21; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Vie Parisienne - San Francisco Chronicle, undated; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Vie Parisienne - Oakland Tribune, 1984 August 4; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
  - Vie Parisienne - Peninsula Times Tribune, 1982 March 1; 1 computer file(s) 1 TIF facsimile
    Owen, Angela M.; Offenbach, Jacques, 1819-1880